nokian900.com 2011-09-30

# Privacy Policy | Nokia N900 Internet Tablet

## [Privacy Policy](http://www.nokian900.com/privacy-policy/ "Permanent Link to Privacy Policy")

#### Posted by Admin on

##### August 26, 2008

We are committed to protecting the privacy and security of the users of our site.

This privacy policy will advise you about how we protect your personal information, and about what choices you have concerning our use of such information. Please read this policy carefully. We may need to change this policy from time to time in order to address new issues and reflect changes on our site. We will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose that information to anyone. Please refer back to this policy regularly.

**Scope Of Privacy Policy**

This policy applies to your use of this site.

**Personal Identification Information**

We don’t request any personal identification information from you (name, email, address, etc).

**Non-Personal Identification Information**

We collect non-personal identification information through the use of:

“Cookie” technology: A “cookie” is an element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system.

“IP address tracking”: An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you are on the Internet. When you request pages from our site, our servers log your IP address.

Non-personal identification information that we collect might include: the browser you use, the type of computer, technical information about your means of connection to our site such as the operating systems and the Internet service providers utilized, and other similar information.

Most browsers are set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, please note that some parts of the site may not function properly.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We also use third party advertisements to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**Google and DoubleClick DART cookies**

We may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by clicking [here](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx "DART Ad-Serving and Search Cookie Opt-Out").

\- Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.

\- Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

\- Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "More details about Google ad and content network privacy policy").

You may view, edit and add to the categories used to provide you with interest-based advertising in the [Ads Preferences Manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences "More details about Ads Preferences Manager").

For more informations about Google Ads privacy policies please visit the [Google Ad and Content Network Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_cookies.html "More details about Google Ad and Content Network Privacy Policy")

**Privacy of Children**

We understand that young people need special safeguards and privacy protection. We realize that they may not understand all the provisions of our policy or be able to make thoughtful decisions about the choices that are made available to our adult users. We strongly urge all parents to participate in their children’s exploration of the Internet and any online services, and to teach their children about protecting their personal information while online.

The site is not directed to children under the age of 13.

**Links To Other Sites**

Users will find advertising or other content on our site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the contents or links that appear on these sites. In addition, these sites or services, including their contents and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies, or no policy (policies) at all. Once you link to another site from our site, you are subject to the terms and conditions of that site, including, but not limited to, its Internet privacy policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third party sites or services before providing any of them with your personal information.

**Disclaimer**

The information provided in this privacy policy should not be considered as giving business, legal, or other advice, or warranting as fail proof, the security of information provided through the Site.

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**

By using our site, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy and any other policies made available to you. If you do not agree to these policies, please do not use our site. Your continued use of the site following the posting of changes to these policies will mean that you accept those changes.
